http://www.hullfc.com/club/club-info/privacy-policy

Hull FC Privacy Policy
We at Hull Super League Limited at the registered address The KCOM Stadium, Walton Street HULL HU3 6HU company registration 3555364 want to make sure all the personal information we have collected about you, is safe and secure whether we collect it through our website at hullfc.com www.hullfc.com or from other sources. This Policy set outs our commitments to you, in compliance with and beyond the General Data Protection Regulation (commonly known as the GDPR) and explains how we collect, store and use your personal information.
We have appointed a Data Protection Officer to oversee our compliance with data protection laws as we are not required to do so, but our General Manager has overall responsibility for data protection compliance in our organisation. If you have any questions about this Policy or what we do with your personal information, their contact details are set out in the “Contact” section below.
To view our Members policy click here
To view our cookie and privacy policy click here
To view our volunteer policy click here
To view our junior members policy click here
To view our competitions policy, click here
Hull FC is part of an organisation which includes but is not limited to Hull Super League Limited, Hull FC Youth in the Community Lottery, and Hull FC Rugby Community Sports and Education Foundation together referred to in this privacy policy as being “Hull”, “we” and/or “us”.
We take the privacy of all of our fans, supporters, customers, web site users, and employees (“customers” / “you”) very seriously and take great care to protect their personal information.
Share Page
Shop News
Featured News
6/04/2020
By picking up items from our brand-new 2020 Spring Training Range, you'll be doing your...
Sponsors
